Tom Hoskins collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - AFC 2011/026: SR059, July 15, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (31 min., 15 sec.): analog, 15 ips; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr059
    - Hop joint
  - AFC 2011/026: SR060, July 15, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (29 min., 7 sec.): analog, 15 ips; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr060
    Original ID #60. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR059; continues on SR061. See notes for SR059.
    - Good morning Miss Carrie
      Hurt sings only part of the song.
    - Richland woman blues
    - [long interview segment]
    - Nobody's dirty business
    - [interview continues]
  - AFC 2011/026: SR061, July 15, 1963; July 23, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (30 min., 37 sec.): analog, 15 ips; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr061
    Original ID #61. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR060; continued on SR062. See notes for SR059.
    - [interview continues]
    - Frankie and Albert
    - Spanish fandang
      Hurt calls this Spanish fandang, although it is sometimes referred to on commercial releases as Spanish fandango.
    - Talking Casey Jones
    - If you don't want me
    - If you don't want me
      Song is cut off at the end of the tape.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR062, July 15, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (31 min., 45 sec.): analog, 15 ips; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr062
    Original ID #62. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR061; continued on SR063. See notes for SR059.
    - If you don't want me
      The beginning of this recording overlaps the end of SR061.
    - Payday
    - Got the blues that can't be satisfied
    - Louis Collins
    - Trouble I had all my days
    - Stagolee
  - AFC 2011/026: SR063, July 15, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (30 min., 48 sec.): analog, 15 ips; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr063
    Original ID #63. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR062; continued on SR064. See notes for SR059.
    - See See Rider
    - Spike driver blues
    - Spike driver blues
    - Make me a pallet on the floor
    - Rubber dolly
    - Salty dog
    - My Creole belle
    - Let the mermaid flirt with me
      Fades out before the song is finished.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR064, July 15, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (40 min., 38 sec.): analog, 15 ips, 2 track, Dolby processed, mono; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr064
    Original ID #64. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR063; continued on SR065. See notes for SR059.
    - Let the mermaid flirt with me
      The beginning of this recording overlaps the end of SR063.
    - Candy man
    - Coffee blues
    - Hey, honey, right away
      Also known as Hey, baby, right away.
    - Sliding Delta
    - Casey Jones
    - Stocktime
    - Lazy blues
    - Beulah land
    - Oh Mary don't you weep
    - When I lay my burden down
      Sometimes referred to as Glory, Glory hallelujah.
    - Keep on knockin' but you can't come in
      Hurt announces the song as I hear you a'knockin' and you can't come in.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR065, July 15, 1963; July 23, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (39 min., 32 sec.): analog, 15 ips, 2 track, Dolby processed, mono; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr065
    Original ID #65. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR064; continued on SR066. See notes for SR059. The first two songs were recorded on July 15; the balance were recorded on July 23.
    - What a friend we have in Jesus
    - Waiting for you
    - Avalon blues
    - Stagolee
    - Over in Gloryland
    - Walking the floor over you
    - Tenting tonight
      Hurt calls the song Camp meeting tonight.
    - Blessed be the name
    - When the roll is called up yonder
    - Royal telephone
    - Blind man sat on the road and cried
    - Where shall I be
  - AFC 2011/026: SR066, July 23, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (40 min., 16 sec.): analog, 15 ips, 2 track, Dolby processed, mono; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr066
    Original ID #66. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR065; continued on SR067. See notes for SR059.
    - Weeping and wailing
    - Bye and bye
      Also known as Farther along.
    - Do Lord remember me
    - Was you there when they crucified my Lord
    - Glory to His name
    - I'll fly away
    - Ten virgins
    - Payday
    - If you don't want me, baby
    - Nobody cares for me
    - Corrina, Corrina
  - AFC 2011/026: SR067, July 23, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (38 min., 46 sec.): analog, 15 ips, full track, mono; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr067
    Original ID #67. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR066; continued on SR068. See notes for SR059.
    - Funky butt
    - Funky butt
    - Cow hookin' blues
    - I'm satisfied
    - Ain't nobody but you
    - The first shot missed him
    - Shortnin' bread
    - Redwing
    - Take me back
    - Four o'clock blues
    - See See rider
    - I got mine
    - Good morning Miss Carrie
  - AFC 2011/026: SR068, July 23, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (30 min., 25 sec.): analog, 15 ips, full track, mono; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr068
    Original ID #68. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR067; continued on SR069. See notes for SR059.
    - Jim Canaan
    - Alabama bound
    - Looking this way
    - Hold to God's unchanging hand
    - Poor boy a long way from home
    - Frankie and Albert
    - Waiting for a train
  - AFC 2011/026: SR069, July 23, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (31 min., 12 sec.): analog; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr069
    Original ID #69. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR068; continued on SR070. See notes for SR059.
    - Liza Jane
      Hurt sings this fragment without accompaniment.
    - Salty dog
    - Chicken song
    - The chicken
      This incorporates the so-called "Chicken song," in which Hurt spells out the word "chicken."
    - Funky butt [more complete version]
      This is a more complete version of the song Hurt sang on SR067.
    - You are my sunshine
    - Will the circle be unbroken
  - AFC 2011/026: SR070, July 23, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (24 min., 32 sec.): analog; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr070
    Original ID #70. Recorded at the Coolidge Auditorium, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. Continued from SR069. See notes for SR059.
    - You got to die
    - [Hurt tells stories]
      The sound fades out at the end of the recording while Hurt is still talking.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR071, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 48 min., 31 sec.; Side B: 48 min., 26 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 2 track, Dolby processed, mono; 10 in.
    Original ID #71.
    - Side A, afc2011026_sr071a
      Recorded before a live audience.
      - Frankie and Albert
      - Spanish fandang
      - Talking Casey Jones
      - Coffee blues
      - Candy man
      - Avalon blues
      - Make me a pallet on the floor
      - Stocktime
      - Sliding Delta
      - Long lonesome blues
      - Waiting for you
        Song is cut off towards the end.
    - Side B, afc2011026_sr071b
      May have been recorded with a small group of people present. Continues on SR072.
      - Make me a pallet on the floor
      - Sliding Delta
      - Candy man
      - Monday morning blues
      - See See rider
      - Stagolee
      - Casey Jones
      - Worried blues
        Another man playing guitar seems to have joined Hurt for this song. The song seems to segue into another blues song (Grouchy blues?), including the line "cook cornbread for your husband, biscuits for your man."
      - Avalon blues
      - Nobody's business
        Song cuts off towards the end.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR072, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (24 min., 39 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 2 track, Dolby B processed, mono; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr072
    Original ID #72. Recorded before a live audience. Continued from SR071b.
    - Nobody's business
    - Coffee blues
    - Let the mermaid flirt with me
    - Richland woman blues
    - Spike driver blues
    - Waiting for you
  - AFC 2011/026: SR073, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 1 hr., 37 min., 46 sec.; Side B: 1 hr., 33 min., 40 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1/2 track, mono; 10 in.
    Original ID #73. Dub of #74 plus the other 5" reel of the rest of the interview. Tom Hoskins conducted the interview; Nick Perls was the recordist.
    - Side A, afc2011026_sr073a
      - [Interview segment]
      - Cow hooking blues
      - Worried blues [?]
      - Monday morning blues
      - Lazy blues
      - [Interview continues]
    - Side B, afc2011026_sr073b
      - [Interview continues]
  - AFC 2011/026: SR074, October 14, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (48 min., 40 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips, 1/2 track, mono; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr074
    Original ID #74. Mississippi John Hurt: biography and stories #3. Tom Hoskins conducted the interview; Nick Perls was the recordist. Recorded at Ontario Place, Washington, D.C.
    - Story about stinging snakes
    - Hurt talks about picking cotton
  - AFC 2011/026: SR075, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 32 min., 11 sec.; Side B: 28 min., 58 sec.): analog; 7 in.
    Original ID #75. Songs and stories at a party. Tom Hoskins is one of the people present (he is heard being called by name more than once). Significant amount of party-related noise. Several people present have guitars.
    - Side A, afc2011026_sr075a
      - [Unidentified]
        Unidentified man sings and plays guitar. Someone is playing slide guitar.
      - Feel like I'm fixin' to die
        Unidentified man sings and plays slide guitar.
      - Stewball
        Performed by Hurt.
      - Funky butt
        The guitar may be played by Hurt, but if he is singing it is not audible.
      - [Unidentified]
        Sung by several people present.
      - [Unidentified]
        May be Hurt singing towards the end of the recording; distortion at the very end of the recording.
    - Side B, afc2011026_sr075b
      - [Several people named: Beverly Dickinson, Dave Evans, and others are identified; Hurt is also present and can be heard at times]
      - My Creole belle
        From this song to the end of the recording, Hurt plays guitar and sings the songs.
      - Shake that thing
      - See See rider
      - [Interview]
  - AFC 2011/026: SR076, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 50 min., 1 sec.; Side B: 1 hr., 4 min., 11 sec.): analog; 7 in.
    Original ID #76. Frank Mizell (blues guitarist). Dick Spottswood was also present. This may have been recorded by Gene Rosenthal at Adelphi Studios circa 1965. Following That's all right, the balance of recording is a dub of commercial sound recordings; possibly 78 rpm discs.
    - Side A, afc2011026_sr076a
      Unidentified female vocalist at times. Recorded in a party-like environment; much background noise. Significant distortion at times.
    - Side B, afc2011026_sr076b
      - When I lay my burden down
        Several people sing (both male and female), and accompany Hurt's guitar with percussion.
      - My Creole belle
        Sung and played by Hurt; accompanied at times by a female vocalist; performance includes hand-clapping. Recording is marred by distortion.
      - [Unidentified]
        Sung and played by Hurt; accompanied at times by a female vocalist; performance includes hand-clapping.
      - Black snake [?]
      - That's all right
  - AFC 2011/026: SR077, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 39 min., 45 sec.; Side B: 14 min., 25 sec.): analog; 7 in.
    Original ID #77.
    - Side A, afc2011026_sr077a
      Frank Mizell (blues guitarist). Songs and storytelling.
    - Side B, afc2011026_sr077b
      Unidentified performers.
      - [Unidentified]
        Male singer with guitar.
      - Mr. Rabbit
        Male singer and female singer, with guitar.
      - Long black veil
        Same performers as the previous song.
      - [Instrumental guitar piece]
        Solo guitar.
      - Cincinnati floor rag
        Probably the same guitarist as the previous tune.
      - Candy man
        Solo male singer/guitarist.
      - [Brief instrumental guitar piece]
        Solo male guitarist.
      - Dust my broom
  - AFC 2011/026: SR078, circa 1964, 1 sound tape reel (1 hr., 2 min., 43 sec.): analog, 7 1⁄2 ips, 1/2 track, mono; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr078
    Original ID #78. Hurt is interviewed by Pete Seeger for Sing out magazine. Most of the recording is the interview, but also includes Hurt singing and playing.
    - [Interview]
    - Tender virgins
    - Let the mermaid flirt with me
    - Nobody's business
    - Stocktime
    - Worried blues
    - Avalon blues
    - Chicken song
  - AFC 2011/026: SR079, 1 sound tape reel (20 min., 57 sec.): analog, 15 ips, stereo; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr079
    - Let the mermaid flirt with me
    - Payday
    - Stagolee
    - Casey Jones
    - Frankie and Albert
  - AFC 2011/026: SR080, 1 sound tape reel (22 min., 23 sec.): analog, 15 ips, stereo; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr080
    - Trouble I've had all my days
    - Pera Lee
      Hurt uses a slide on his guitar.
    - See See Rider
    - Louis Collins
    - Coffee blues
    - Nobody's business
    - Do Lord remember me
    - Monday morning blues
  - AFC 2011/026: SR081, 1928; March 3, 1963, 1 sound tape reel (1 hr., 04 min., 52 sec.): analog, 15 ips or 7 1/2 ips; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr081a
    The first song is a dub of the 1928 Okeh recording of Hurt performing Avalon blues. SR088 is a copy of the same recording. Some selections are from March 3, 1963, while others are from performances at various venues.
    - Avalon blues
    - Cow hookin' blues [instrumental version]
      See SR015a.
    - John talks about his life and history (others interject along the way)
    - Ain't nobody but you
    - Make me a pallet on the floor
    - Sliding Delta
      Sung by an unidentified man and then by Hurt, who plays guitar throughout.
    - Make me a pallet on the floor
      This is a different version from the previous one on the same recording.
    - Monday morning blues
    - [Hurt tells stories]
    - Stagolee
    - Worried blues
    - Avalon blues
  - AFC 2011/026: SR082, circa 1964, 1 sound tape reel (46 min.): analog; 10 in.; afc2011026_sr082
    Partial dub of interview recording with Pete Seeger (SR082); spoken word section only.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR087, circa 1963-1966, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 48 min., 37 sec.; Side B: 10 min., 23 sec.): analog; 7 in.
    Interview with Hurt.
    - Side A, afc2011026_sr087a
      - Interview
    - Side B, afc2011026_sr087b
      - The welcome address
        Hurt credits Holly Ochs as co-writer of the song.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR088, 1 sound tape reel (41 min., 53 sec.): analog, 7 1⁄2 ips, 1/2 track, mono; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr088
    According to notes in the tape box, this is a compilation of Hurt recordings made for Maynard Solomon for the lawsuit with Vanguard. The recordings are from the "Music Rsesearch vaults" (i.e., Music Research, Inc.).
  - AFC 2011/026: SR089, 1 sound tape reel (37 min., 51 sec.): analog, 7 1⁄2 ips, 1/2 track, mono; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr089
    interview
  - AFC 2011/026: SR090, 1 sound tape reel (Side A: 12 min., 44 sec.; Side B: 1 hr., 4 min., 26 sec.): analog, 4 track; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr090
    Dub of commercial recordings, possibly opera; recorded in a language other than English. Side A may have print through; a second recording (unrelated to this collection) can be heard simultaneously during playback.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR091, 1 sound tape reel (23 min., 49 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr091
    Dub of one or more commercial sound recordings (nothing by Hurt).
  - AFC 2011/026: SR092, 1 sound tape reel (21 min., 59 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr092
    Dub of a ragtime music compilation LP, Side B only (Piedmont 13158-B).
  - AFC 2011/026: SR093, 1 sound tape reel (23 min., 22 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr093
  - AFC 2011/026: SR094, 1 sound tape reel (21 min., 50 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr094
  - AFC 2011/026: SR095, 1 sound tape reel (21 min., 29 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr095
    Dub of a compilation LP of 12-string guitar music, Side A only. (Piedmont 13159-A)).
  - AFC 2011/026: SR096, 1 sound tape reel (21 min., 34 sec.): analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr096
    Dub of a commercial disc sound recording of Corrina, Corrina. See note for SR098.
  - AFC 2011/026: SR097, 1 sound tape reel (21 min., 24 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr097
  - AFC 2011/026: SR098, 1 sound tape reel (21 min., 44 sec.): analog; 7 in.; afc2011026_sr098
    Dub of the same recording as SR096.
- Series III: Graphic Images
  Some of the photos were used as legal evidence in the court case brought by the Hurt family against Hoskins.
  - Avalon, Mississippi, March 1963 (Box-folder 5/1)
    6 black-and-white photos taken in Avalon, measuring 4 1/2 in. x 3 1/4 in. Two have notes in red ballpoint ink along a border. Photos show the exterior of Hurt's home, a nearby store, and an unidentified man.
  - Avalon, Mississippi, April 1963 (Box-folder 5/2)
    6 black-and-white photos of Hurt, taken in front of his home; measuring 4 1/2 in. x 3 1/4 in.
  - Avalon, Mississippi, January 23, 1965 (Box-folder 5/3)
    2 black-and-white photos taken in front of the post office in Avalon. One photo measures 5 in. x 4 in., and the other is slightly smaller (the bottom edge has been cut off). The complete photo shows Hurt holding a sunburst guitar; another man stands next to him (described on the other photo's verso as his "buddy"), and a third, unidentified man stands at left. The cropped photo shows only Hurt and his friend.
  - Avalon, Mississippi, April 1965 (Box-folder 5/4)
    25 3 in. x 5 in. black-and-white photos taken in Avalon. Another, smaller photo was trimmed from a larger photo. While the date stamp on the border says April 1965, it is evident some of the photos were taken in March, as the unidentified man in those photos also appears in the so-called April 1965 photos. The photos show Hurt and his wife Jessie in front of their home, group of men at the gas station, livestock, and the unidentified man seen in the March 1963 photos.
  - Avalon, Mississippi (Box-folder 5/5)
    12 4 in. x 5 in. black-and-white photos and 3 8 in. x 10 in. black-and-white photos, taken in Avalon; Hoskins may appear in one photo with Hurt. Most of the photos were taken of Hurt near what appears to be a disused canal or waterway, sometimes with a guitar. Some photos show Hurt and the guitar (which may have belonged to Hoskins) on the steps of his home.
  - Unidentified boy, holding a guitar, February 17, 1970 (Box-folder 5/6)
    Black-and-white Polaroid photo, measuring 3 1/2 in. x 4 1/4 in. This may be Hurt's grandson: the hat looks like the one usually worn by Hurt. The child is wearing a Cub Scout uniform.
  - Photo by Seth Beckerman, circa 1963-1966 (Box-folder 5/7)
    1 8 in. x 10 in. black-and-white photo of Hurt in concert.
  - Photos by Bob Campbell (Robert James Campbell), circa 1963-1966 (Box-folder 5/8)
    3 8 in. x 10 in. black-and-white contact sheets of 35mm images (and some cut-out pieces of contact sheets). Photos taken at the Gaslight Cafe, in New York.
  - Photos by Stephen C. (Steve) LaVere (photocopies), 1964 (Box-folder 5/9)
    Photocopies of 2 black-and-white 8 in. x 10 in. photos and 2 black-and-white contact sheets of 35mm images. Taken at the 1964 Newport Folk Festival. Fred and Annie McDowell appear in the 8 in. x 10 in. photos. The contact sheet includes the same images, plus other scenes, including Hurt performing onstage.
  - Photos by Jim Mahan, September 11, 1963 (Box-folder 5/10)
    8 black-and-white contact sheets of 35mm images, taken at a coffee house in Washington, D.C.
  - Photos by J. Robert (Bob) Mantler, circa 1963-1966 (Box-folder 5/11)
    One 8 in. x 10 in. black-and-white photo of Hurt, with a matching copy negative. Two 8 in x 10 in. black-and-white contact sheets, with a total of 18 frames showing Hurt playing or posing with a guitar. An envelope with Mantler's name is included in the folder. The 8 in. x 10 in. image may have been used for an album called "Legacy."
  - Photos by Jim Marshall, circa July 23-26, 1964; undated (Box-folder 5/12)
    1 8 in. x 10 in. black and white photo of Elizabeth Cotten and Hurt posing (off-stage) at the Newport Folk Festival, 1964. Two 8 in. x 10 in. photos of hurt, onstage (undated), plus an envelope labeled with the return address of Stefan Grossman's Guitar Workshop, and sent to Hoskins. Also, a slip of paper that accompanies the photos, noted that an item (unidentified) was an exhibit in a legal case.
  - Photo by Rick Sullo (Box-folder 5/13)
    1 black-and-white 8 in. x 10 in. close-up photo of Hurt.
  - Photos by Paul S. Ulrich, 1964 (Box-folder 5/14)
    5 black-and-white 8 in. x 10 in. photos of Hurt on stage, during a concert with Pete Seeger at Lisner Auditorium, Washington, D.C. (December 12, 1964). 1 black-and-white 8 in. x 10 in. of Hurt at the blues workshop, Philadelphia Folk Festival (1964).
  - Photo proofs, circa 1963-1966 (Box-folder 5/15)
    3 black-and-white photo proofs, one measuring approximately 7 1/4 in. x 7 3/4 in, and two approximately 7 1/4 in. x 9 1/2 in.
  - Photos from the Newport Folk Festival, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 5/16)
    Three 8 1/2 in. x 14 in. photocopies of contact sheets showing Hurt at Newport (1963); the photographer is John Byrne Cooke (son of Alistair Cooke). One photocopy of an uncredited photo from Newport in 1964, with Hurt and Elizabeth Cotten.
  - Three contact sheets, circa 1963-1966 (Box-folder 5/17)
    3 8 in. x 10 in. black-and-white contact sheets of 35mm images. Each sheet represents the work of a different photographer: Cogan (probably Michael Cogan), Karovitch (no other information), and Bobbi Lord.
  - Contact sheets from an unidentified photographer, circa 1963-1966 (Box-folder 5/18)
    6 8 in. x 10 in. black-and-white contact sheets of 35mm images
  - Still photos of moving image film, circa 1963-1966 (Box-folder 5/19)
    5 8 in. x 10 in. black-and-white photos of film, showing Hurt playing guitar (see MV01 for the moving images from which these frames were copied). Some images show him without a hat. Three images have edge code: two copies of the same image have 14722 and another image has 14719. A separate group of items are strips and pieces of paper, in various sizes, with still frames from the film. These function as proofs (handwritten notations on some of them).
  - Images and related documentation, circa 1963-1966 (Box-folder 5/20)
    4 8 in. x 10 in. black-and-white photos and 1 8 3/4 in. x 9 1/2 in. print of a negative. Related documentation includes contact information for Lucille Hurt and for Paul Ulrich, as well as photocopies of photos, a draft of an essay for a commercial release on King Bee Records, a photocopied magazine article about Hurt that mentions Hoskins, and a manila envelope with handwritten notes.
  - Color slides (Box-folder 5/21)
    21 35mm Ektachrome color slides, showing Hurt in performance (close-ups). Accompanied by the original slide mount display, plus a slip of paper indicating these slides were submitted as an exhibit in a legal case.
  - Skip James (photo, circa 1960s ) (Box-folder 5/22)
    Black-and-white photo of Skip James, measuring 4 1/2 in. x 2 3/4 in.; relocated from folder 1/10.
- Series IV: Moving Images
  - AFC 2011/026: MV01, March 14, 1965, 1 videocassette (VHS; 11 min., 39 sec.): analog
    Video copied from a film original. "Jacobson" (from the slate) is probably Joel Jacobson.
    - Mississippi John test roll #2 Jacobson Unity